

5104 Proper Tunghaan Minglanilla, Cebu 6046 ADDRESS

(+63) 943 221 9155 PHONE

johnlloydmayol@gmail.com E-MAIL

https://github.com/mayol27

www.linkedin.com/in/johnlloyd-mayol LINKEDIN

https://join.skype.com/invite/XI uGRihGz2Zf

SKYPE

https://mayol27.github.io

ABOUT ME

A skilled IT affluent young professional with more than 1 years of experience in Development Software & Hardware Design, Software Maintenance and Repair, and Graphics Design with enhancing PHP in Programming Languages Codelgniter, (Laravel, Wordpress, CSS, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, GIT, and Yarn).

SKILLS

WORK

LARAVEL

CODEIGNITER

JOHN LLOYD SEGISMAR MAYOL

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

EXPERIENCE

(November 2019 – Present)

HiPE Inc.

Software Developer

- + Maintaining company website
 - Wordpress (ACF, Elementor, and Ninja Form)
 - Editing Photo (Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator)
- + Maintaining client website BUKKENOH 物件王
 - Laravel, SASS, CSS, HTML, GIT, and Yarn

(October 2019)

Devcash

THESIS

A SOFTWARE-AS-A-SERVICE FOR CASHIERING SYSTEM FOR MICRO AND SMALL ENTERPRISES

Position: Hipster

Language: AngularJS, PHP, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, Android, and Firebase

(October 2018 - May 2019)

KREDO IT ABROD INC.

ON-THE JOB TRAINING

- + Hardware and Software Technical Support
- + Created Inventory System for the company

(May 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU - MAIN CAMPUS

WORKING SCHOLAR

- + Hardware and Software Technical Support
- + Assisting students and teachers on computer laboratory
- + Sorting and filing documents

EDUCATION

(June 2015 - October 2019)

University of Cebu – Main Campus

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

(June 2011 - March 2015)

Immaculate Heart of Mary Academy – Minglanilla HIGH SCHOOL

ORGANIZATION

(March 2017 – Present)

GDG Cebu - Google Developers Group

(April 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU – ASSOCIATION OF WORKING SCHOLARS (AWS)

(June 2015 - October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU – PHILIPPINE SOCIETY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY STUDENT (PSITS)

Wordpress

PHP

ANGULARJS

MYSQL

SASS

BOOTSTRAP

CSS

HTML

GIT

YARN

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

TROUBLESHOOT

PERSONALITY

COMMUNICATION

ORGANIZATION

TEAM PLAYER

CREATIVITY

SOCIAL

CERTIFICATES

(2018)

Building Entrepreneurial Ecosystem to Enhance Higher Education Value-Added for Better Graduate Employability (BEEHIVE) – MOOC

(2017)

5th UC-ICT Congress "Sharpening Junior Mobile Technologists"

(2016)

4th UC-ICT Congress "Shaping up Creative Minds through Great UX Design"

REFERENCE

Ms. Ma. Catherine Carumba

Secretary – College of Computer Studies

Contact: 255 – 7777 loc. 113

Ms. Lina J. Perez

UCEMPC – Secretary

Contact: 255 - 7777 loc. 136

Ms. Jerrah Marie Son

Laboratory Supervisor – CCS

Contact: 0923 - 866 - 7880